When you were here be fore
Couldn't look you in the eye
You're just like an an gel
Your skin makes me cry
You float like a fea ther
In a beauti ful world
I wish I was spe cial
You're so fucking spe cial
But I'm a creep
I'm a weir do
What the hell am I doing here?
I don't be long here
I don't care if it hurts
I wanna have con trol
I want a perfect bo dy
I want a perfect soul
I want you to no tice
When I'm not a round
You're so fucking spe cial
I wish I was spe cial
But I'm a creep
I'm a weir do
What the hell am I doing here?
I don't be long here
Oh, oh
She's run ning out the door
She's run ning out
She run, run, run, run
Run
Whatever makes you ha ppy
Whatever you want
You're so fucking spe cial
I wish I was spe cial
But I'm a creep
I'm a weir do
What the hell am I doing here?
I don't be long here